A Guide to the Vouchers for new treasury warrants from the Virginia Land Office, 1787-1948
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Vouchers for new treasury warrants from the Virginia Land Office, 1787-1948
The Library of Virginia
LOI 24
1.5 cu ft (10 boxes)
Virginia. Land Office.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession LOI 24 transferred by the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1948.
Historical Information
The act which established the previous Land Office passed the General Assembly on 22 June 1779. The register was the head of the Office and was appointed by joint ballot of both houses of the legislature.
Scope and Content
These records contain printed vouchers, signed by the state auditor, on which warrants were issued. Each voucher contains the amount of money paid into the treasury by an individual and the number of acres to which this sum entitled him. The basis for the allowance, whether by the act establishing the Land Office or by any one of several special acts under which land was available, is also recorded. The records cover the period from 1787 to 1948. After 1926, each warrants include a certificate addressed to surveyors, a receipt, and sometimes a cover letter from the Comptroller's Office. Many of the warrant numbers covered in the range are not present, either because they were not used or because the warrants are missing.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Virginia. Auditor of Public Accounts; Virginia. Auditor of Public Accounts (1776-1928); Virginia. Land Office; Virginia. Office of the Second Auditor.
subjects:
Land grants -- Virginia.
Genre and Form Terms:
State government records.; Vouchers.
Contents List
- New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, 1786-1948., Extent: 10 boxes (1.5 cu. ft.). (Box 1-10)
  Chronological
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 1-999, 1786-1794. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 200-699, 1794. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 700-1097, 1794-1795. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 1098-1499, 1795. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 1500-1799, 1795-1796. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 1800-2099, 1796-1797. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 2100-2399, 1797-1798. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 2400-2699, 1798-1799. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 2700-2999, 1799-1800. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 3000-3300, 1800-1801. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 3301-3599, 1801-1803. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 3600-3899, 1803-1804. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 3900-4199, 1804-1805. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 4200-4399, 1805-1807. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 4400-4599, 1807-1809. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 4600-4799, 1809-1811. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 4800-5099, 1811-1813. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 5100-5350, 1813-1815. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 5351-5599, 1815-1816. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 5600-5899, 1816-1817. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 5900-6200, 1817-1818. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 6201-7299, 1818-1822. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 7300-7499, 1822-1823. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 7500-7799, 1823-1824. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 7800-7999, 1824-1825. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 8000-9099, 1825-1826. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 9100-9900, 1826-1828. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 10000-10199, 1828-1829. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 10200-10399, 1829-1830. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 10400-10499, 1830. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 10500-10699, 1830-1832. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 10700-10899, 1832-1833. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 10900-11099, 1833. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 11100-12299, 1833-1838. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 12300-12499, 1835-1836. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 12500-12699, 1836. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 12700-12899, 1836-1837. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 12900-13999, 1837-1838. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 14000-14199, 1838-1839. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 14200-14399, 1839-1840. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 14400-14599, 1840-1841. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 14600-14899, 1841-1842. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 14900-15199, 1842-1843. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 15200-15499, 1843-1845. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 15500-15799, 1845. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 15800-16099, 1845-1846. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 16100-16399, 1846-1847. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 16400-16699, 1847. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 16700-16999, 1847-1848. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 17000-17299, 1848. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 17300-17599, 1848-1849. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 17600-17899, 1849. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 17900-18199, 1849-1850. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 18200-18299, 1850. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 18300-18499, 1850. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 18500-18699, 1850. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 18700-18912, 1850. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 18913-24826, 1838-1858. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 24827-24999, 1858. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 25000-25248, 1858. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 25249-32361, 1867-1880. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 32362-32399, 1926-1927. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 32400-32499, 1927-1931. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 32500-32550, 1931-1936. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 32551-32599, 1936-1942. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, Nos. 32600-33647, 1943-1948. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - New Treasury Warrant Vouchers, unnumbered, 1783-1835. (Box 10, Folder 3)